[
  {
    "question": "In which US national park would you find the Grand Prismatic Spring?",
    "no-open": true,
    "answers": [
      "Yellowstone",
      "Yosemite",
      "Zion",
      "Sequoia"
    ],
    "correct": "Yellowstone",
    "source": "https://www.wanderlust.co.uk/content/national-parks-trivia-quiz/"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which US national park would you find this unique rock formation?",
    "no-open": true,
    "answers": [
      "Big Bend, Texas",
      "Arches, Utah",
      "Grand Canyon, Arizona",
      "Monument Valley, Arizona"
    ],
    "correct": "Arches, Utah"
  },
  {
    "question": "Where in the world would you find Torres del Paine National Park?",
    "no-open": true,
    "answers": [
      "Chile",
      "Argentina",
      "Chile & Argentina",
      "Nice try! It's obviously Brazil"
    ],
    "correct": "Chile"
  },
  {
    "question": "Costa Rica’s Tortuguero National Park is named after its most famous residents. What does the name mean?",
    "no-open": true,
    "answers": [
      "The tortured forest",
      "Land of tortoises",
      "Forest of sea turtles",
      "Turtle catcher"
    ],
    "correct": "Turtle catcher"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which African country would you find the zebra-packed Etosha National Park?",
    "no-open": true,
    "answers": [
      "South Africa",
      "Namibia",
      "Zimbabwe",
      "Tanzania"
    ],
    "correct": "Namibia"
  },
  {
    "question": "The Great Migration of wildebeest involves two African national parks. Can you name those parks?",
    "no-open": true,
    "answers": [
      "Serengeti and Tarangire",
      "Masai Mara and Serengeti",
      "Chobe and Masai Mara",
      "Kruger and Masai Mara"
    ],
    "correct": "Masai Mara and Serengeti"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these four African national parks is the largest?",
    "no-open": true,
    "answers": [
      "Maiko, Congo DRC",
      "Chobe, Botswana",
      "Ngorongoro, Tanzania",
      "Kruger, South Africa"
    ],
    "correct": "Kruger, South Africa"
  },
  {
    "question": "Croatia is known for its breathtaking national parks. But how many does it have in total?",
    "no-open": true,
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "8",
      "9",
      "10"
    ],
    "correct": "8"
  },
  {
    "question": "Three of these national parks are technically considered to be in France. One isn’t. Can you spot the odd one out?",
    "no-open": true,
    "answers": [
      "Guiana Amazonian",
      "Guadeloupe",
      "Kaieteur",
      "Vanoise"
    ],
    "correct": "Kaieteur"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these national parks is the largest in the UK?",
    "no-open": true,
    "answers": [
      "Cairngorms, Scotland",
      "Snowdonia, Wales",
      "Lake District, England",
      "Dartmoor, England"
    ],
    "correct": "Cairngorms, Scotland"
  },
  {
    "question": "Yala National Park is a dream safari spot for leopard lovers. Where exactly would you find it?",
    "no-open": true,
    "answers": [
      "Bangladesh",
      "India",
      "Bhutan",
      "Sri Lanka"
    ],
    "correct": "Sri Lanka"
  },
  {
    "question": "Can you identify this Asian national park from its jagged mountain top?",
    "no-open": true,
    "answers": [
      "Nikko, Japan",
      "Seoraksan, South Korea",
      "Ranthambore, India",
      "Shei-Pa, Taiwan"
    ],
    "correct": "Seoraksan, South Korea"
  },
  {
    "question": "Is Antarctica technically classed as a national park?",
    "no-open": true,
    "answers": [
      "Yes, ALL of Antarctica is a national park",
      "No, but it is classed as a Special Conservation Area",
      "There is at least one national park in Antarctica",
      "Nice try! It’s not like you can protect ice…"
    ],
    "correct": "No, but it is classed as a Special Conservation Area"
  },
  {
    "question": "In which Australian national park would you find this eye-catching rock?",
    "no-open": true,
    "answers": [
      "Kakadu",
      "Uluru-Kata Tjuta",
      "Karijini",
      "Nice try! It’s not in Australia"
    ],
    "correct": "Uluru-Kata Tjuta"
  },
    {
    "question": "Croatia is known for its breathtaking national parks. But how many does it have in total?",
    "no-open": true,
    "answers": [
      "Simien Mountains, Ethiopia",
      "Haleakala, Hawaii",
      "Tongariro, New Zealand",
      "Masaya Volcano, Nicaragua"
    ],
    "correct": "Tongariro, New Zealand"
  },
  {
    "question": "The world's biggest national park is...?",
    "no-open": true,
    "answers": [
      "Northeast Greenland, Greenland",
      "Jasper, Canada",
      "Fjordland, New Zealand",
      "Yellowstone, USA"
    ],
    "correct": "Northeast Greenland, Greenland"
  },
  {
    "question": "Now you know the correct answer: how BIG do you think the world’s largest national park is?",
    "no-open": true,
    "answers": [
      "1,034,000 sq km",
      "972,000 sq km",
      "706,000 sq km",
      "481,500 sq km"
    ],
    "correct": "972,000 sq km"
  }
]